theautoinsurance.com 2012-05-02

# Privacy Policy |

This privacy statement covers the site www.Theautoinsurance.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Daniel Wesley at [support@theautoinsurance.com](mailto:support@creditloan.com.)

**Disclosure of Information**

Theautoinsurance.com will not sell, trade, share or rent your personal information to others. In fact, we do not even log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. We may use IP addresses to compile and provide aggregate statistics about our visitors, traffic patterns, and administer the site. This statistical information may also be related to third parties, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We collect only the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services, such as your name and e-mail addresses only. We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations.

**Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of young children is important to us. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information at our sites from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our site is structured to attract anyone under 18. This email address is being protected from spam bots, you need Javascript enabled to view it

**Copyright Notice**

All materials contained in this website are protected by federal copyright laws, and may not be reproduced, republished, distributed, displayed, or otherwise exploited in any manner without the express prior written permission of Theautoinsurance.com.

We have staff members who routinely check for copyright violations and content duplication. Federal legal action will be taken against anyone found using Theautoinsurance.com articles and/or content with expressed written permissions.

**Contact**

If you have questions or comments, email us at [support@theautoinsurance.com](mailto:support@visualeconomics.com) This email address is being protected from spam bots, you need Javascript enabled to view it ,

Note: If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**Copyright © 2009. Theautoinsurance.com**
